Hi everyone, nice to meet you!
My name is Katia Cerrus-
or you can call me Katia, just like everyone else did.
I'm a cerberus who works as Hell's gatekeeper.
One could simply say i'm a security guard.. hehe~
As a Cerberus, i have 3 different personalities.
First, we have Kat-
who's actually the person you're listening to right now.
Then, we have Kati-
the 'cold and sarcastic' second-eldest daughter.
Say hi, Kati!
[Kati]
Hi everyone, (yeah..)
Nice to meet you, my name is Kati..
So yeah, just call me Kati.
[Kat]
And yeah!
Last but not least, we have the youngest daughter which is-
Tia! she's quite a shy one that's-
Simply the "shy-shy" type!
Come on Tia, say hi!
U-Uh...
U-Uhm...
H-Hi everyone..
M-My name is- Tia!
N-Nice to meet you..
So... there lies our Introduction as-
Katia Cerrus!
And also, don't forget to hold on tight for our Debut Stream!
That's it for today, everyone!
I'll be signing off as Katia Cerrus.
See you next time!~
#OtsuSinners!